all-americanheroes.net 2019-07-17

# 

Privacy Notice   
Effective Date: 4/25/2017 

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for this website. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following: 

What information we collect;  
With whom it is shared;  
How it can be corrected;  
How it is secured;  
How policy changes will be communicated; and  
How to address concerns over misuse of personal data.

Information Collection, Use, and Sharing 

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We may share this information to our marketing partners. 

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We may share your information when we think you may benefit from marketing information that you may receive from our marketing partners. 

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. 

Your Access to and Control Over Information 

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided on our website: 

See what data we have about you, if any. Change/correct any data we have about you. Express any concern you have about our use of your data. 

Security 

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. We do not collect credit card information. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

Notification of Changes 

You may check this page to find updates to this policy. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately at sbisupport1@gmail.com.
